Good evening, everyone.
Good evening.
This is Juice Wonderland TV, a member of Berryz KOBO.
Welcome.
Where's Hyorin?
Huh?
Hyorin is on a family vacation,
Today, we would like to do a project with 5 members.
Five!
Oh? Huh?
Let me tell you a lie,
Today, I'm going to surprise Hyo-rin.
Oh! Here we go again.
What do you think the surprise will be?
What?
What do you think? What is it?
I don't know,
The surprise was a pain in the ass, wasn't it?
The opening talk is over.
We did it!
And it's been a while!
There hasn't been much of a gap. Not much at all.
But Hiyori's reaction is so funny.
I love Hiyorin's reaction!
I love it!
We all have to do our best to talk!
Let's have fun!
I'll do my best!
How long do you think it'll take?
Here we go!
Akimoto Ki Barameter Chosho TV
Hello everyone!
Thank you for watching today!
Oh, by the way, I bet you're all out there right now, chatting in real time.
Chatting?
That's why you're watching the premiere.
I'm sure it's because you're watching.
I've been commenting a lot.
I'm doing that.
And I'm doing it on my account.
So, please, everybody, comment a lot.
I'd appreciate it.
I've been doing a lot of projects like this lately.
My project
Main project
The important thing is
I know we're all doing lessons and stuff, but
I've got a new one for you this time too.
We're all here.
We've got a new one for you.
We're doing it on the side.
Thank you very much.
We had a good time at the top side.
We had a great time.
I still don't have a picture of you on the side.
Me too.
I'm gone, too.
My favorite item.
What?
Huh?
Give me that.
No, no, no.
What's wrong with this candy?
The shock is too much.
No, Chiba took care of that.
The packs, the beauty stuff...
There's so much beauty stuff.
There's tons of it.
Bath salts and stuff.
This one is beautiful.
I put bath salts in it every day.
That's nice.
So it's not like the other ones you've had.
Not even close.
I'm glad I got you your old pack and bath salts.
I'm glad.
And some energy drinks.
Nutritional drink.
Pack inside
Drink inside
I love
I love it!
I was happy with the drink
And the drinks.
Thank you so much!
But, Obara-chan, I'd like to hold your hand too.
Oh, I see.
Then...
Obara-chan, here.
Then, from now on...
I'll make it colorful.
Okay?
That's great, Lily.
Well, we're not done here yet.
Okay, here we go.
Oh, shit!
Okay, I'm going to go get an accordion.
Can someone connect me?
Connect me, please.
I'll be your recorder.
No, no, no, no, no.
What's this?
What is this?
A machine like this.
Like this.
Ah, ah,
New project like this
Like this
A foot around this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Can't we?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Let's just get out of here.
Maybe we can make a circle.
That's a good idea.
I can do it. I can do it. I can do it.
How about this?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, wow.
Here.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, yeah.
What's that?
It's now yen.
Yen.
No, no, no.
Bye, bye, bye, bye
bye bye bye bye
bye bye bye bye bye bye
What do you mean?
What
Who?
Wow.
I knew you were going to win.
So...
What?
We did a 2D side-by-side concert.
We're going on the Idol Cruise.
We're going on a cruise? I don't know...
What's with the angry looks on people's faces?
I don't know.
I like it.
It's cute.
Me.
What's that?
Let's go.
Ready?
Superlative. Ikaralina.
I'll get behind you, bye member.
Top of the line, Ikarina!
We're not going to let you do this. It's the Audemars Piguet Birthday!
Everybody's mad at me.
They're mad at me again.
They're still mad.
Still mad?
I won't let them.
Who's still mad?
You're still mad at me.
I'm scary when I'm angry.
You're scary when you're angry.
If I get mad, you'll really lose me.
I'll just keep showing up, Caplin.
I'm afraid that if I get mad, you won't get mad at me.
When I say I'm mad, I don't mean I'm mad.
You're right.
I'm scared when I'm mad.
What have you been mad about lately?
What have I been angry about lately?
Have you been angry recently?
Sit down
Sit down.
Why are you standing there?
It's not that I get angry. It's just that I always have to be careful.
There's a traffic light coming up.
I tell everyone I'm going to run.
We're getting close.
That's sweet.
Why can't we run closer?
No, not so close.
We have to cross quickly in the neighborhood.
There are cars you want to protect.
I can't let that car cross.
You're gonna get him in trouble.
We can't be too close.
Let's go.
You're early. From now on.
I was here quite a while ago.
I jumped.
I love you, Grandpa.
I'm sure it'll lead to something else after today.
Did you guys see this?
I'm here at the live company in Yokohama.
I'm watching it. I don't watch it every day.
I can say that every day. Seriously.
I realized something at one point.
What?
It was something about the lami lami girl.
The wobbly girl.
Heroine's awakening.
There's also a blackout.
What's with the bangs?
Okay, like, I can't do it to hijo.
Because it's like this.
Embarrassing.
It's growing into a label.
Which one was it?
The producer.
The Disney car producer.
Oh, no!
Producer.
Cutting.
Hey, no!
No!
I'm sorry.
That's embarrassing.
It's not good enough.
That's for sure.
So, you know, it's a project.
Like cute or cool,
If you're asked to do something like that.
I think I'd rather be in my pants.
Let's go.
I'm in it, I'm in it, I'm in it.
I'm in my pants.
The camera guy came in.
Failed.
Cryptol.
Rejected.
Unique.
Failed.
Why?
I can't do it next time.
Yes, but...
But..,
Yes, I know.
What? What? What?
I'm feeling it.
I know.
That's why,
What? What? What?
It's impossible to do it now.
Well, that's true.
But it's gonna crack.
It's gonna crack.
I'll glare at it.
We have to glare.
But a glare?
What do you mean, glare?
I'm gonna glare.
That's how live shows work.
I glare a little during the show.
A glare like yours is important.
Hito-chan is great when she's relaxed.
Like Hito-chan.
You know...
After you make a face like you're going to eat your dinner.
Eat your dinner.
What kind of face?
Before the black dive.
I have that look.
Listen to me.
That's me.
That's how I looked before the Black Dive.
Before Black Dive...
You know, there's something a little funny about it.
I'm so self-disciplined.
Eat your dinner.
Oh, my God.
After the "eat your dinner" look.
And then a really intense look in his eyes.
Eat your dinner.
It's a "eat your dinner" expression.
It's funny.
Eat your dinner.
I want to say something.
Oh, I'm in pain.
Congratulations on your iron.
You're gonna want to tell me.
You want to say it to me.
I'm going to eat dinner with all my fans.
You didn't say that?
You're making a face.
Your face.
Do you guys do Arographis?
Yes, we do.
Have you decided on the show?
Yeah, it's set.
I hope you'll keep an eye out for it.
Yes, I'll do my best.
I've been getting a lot of compliments on the show.
I was so happy.
To Mr. Vitarmus.
To Mr. VITALMUS
It's not so much that it's great.
I'm not saying it's great, I'm just
I'm just saying
I'm going to take a proper risk with the putty.
That's right.
I'll take it.
I think there's a lot of things that didn't work.
but as a live performance, it was good.
like that.
I'm a little teary.
Hey, hey, hey!
I was so happy, wasn't I?
The staff really cried too much this time.
She really cried too much.
It's really the staff's fault this time.
It's not our fault you cried so much this time.
They're important.
Of course.
I mean, I'm touched, but...
I was moved, but I held it in.
But those tears...
After the show.
When I was involved...
I'm glad I got involved.
They're holding the venue and everything.
I'm so glad I was able to be a part of it.
I wasn't really happy like that.
I was happy.
I was very happy.
I'm happy to be a part of a group
I want to be a group that people are happy to be a part of.
I want to do my best to be a group that people love.
I will do my best.
Thank you very much.
Now that that's all said and done...
What time is it now, ladies and gentlemen?
What minute is it?
What was the minute?
Ten minutes.
That's it.
Thank you very much.
Bye.
I said, "Does it look good on me?
It looked good on you.
Oh, Hiyori suddenly
I tried to connect it to something cute.
But it didn't work.
I spilled it all over the house.
But, you know, it was the first time.
I thought you already knew.
It's been a little long.
I noticed it the last time before that.
I was still aware of it the time before.
And when you pretend?
I can pretend.
I don't know.
Hiyori.
Staring at each other.
It's okay.
You didn't tell me.
That's right.
By the way, what's the best time?
I don't know.
What kind of surprise?
The next one after the last one.
The one they wouldn't let me plan for so long.
This surprise.
The opening.
It never ends.
The never-ending opening.
What is this surprise?
Which one is it?
You talk too fast.
Silence becomes scary.
The members who usually don't talk are talking a lot.
Yes, everyone is talking.
Everyone is talking so much.
Everyone is talking so hard.
It was difficult.
But it was kind of loud.
I really don't know why it started.
It was like a one-man show.
Stop it!
It's like holding hands.
I thought I could solve it, and when I did, it turned out to be an act.
That's so good.
That, that, that.
I can't get over the feeling of solving it before you.
I want to do a new pattern.
I want people to enjoy it.
I think we can call it "Surprise" too.
I noticed.
Where did everyone notice?
They didn't notice it from the beginning.
On the contrary,
But, you know, it could be.
Just change the title to "NIRAMEKKO DOKKURI" at the beginning,
At the very least, it's deceptive.
But I want to see NIRAMEKKO. I want to see NIRAMECCO.
I want to see NIRAMECCO.
I'm sure there were a lot of recent developments,
Next time, I wonder who set it up and where.
I wonder if there will be a reverse surprise?
Everyone, except me,
I wonder if I have to go to the corner and continue talking on my own.
Would Pia try to surprise us in the opposite direction?
I wonder if she'll get into the groove and mix it up with this fugiton.
I was thinking about that kind of thing so much, thinking about what's going on behind the scenes.
I'm too suspicious, right?
So you never know when and where things will happen.
Be careful.
So, how long can we continue this opening talk?
When will Pia notice?
It was a surprise!
Thank you very much!
See you again!
Shine!
You look like you're crying.
Turn the umbrella around and take it easy
Otherwise I wouldn't be able to walk
I'm sure there's someone crying somewhere
And somewhere you'll get wet again
I hope it's not too cold
I'm sure that somewhere someone is crying
Just a little bit of my feelings
I want to share it with you
I still don't know what's in front of me
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Good bye Good bye Thank you for yesterday
After the rain, the cityscape turns color
On the canvas of my broken heart
Paint a piece of the future
And it's guiding me on the way
I can tell you now
And the reason for my tears. Whenever I'm lost, I'll remember it right away.
And when it rains, I'll try to smile
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are sparkling
My heart is like a sunny sky, rainbow pools, making rainbow sounds
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are sparkling
My heart is like a rainbow, spilling every tear
I'm wearing a rainbow dress
Please subscribe to our channel!